Guide to the Albert Hazen Wright Papers, 1820-1960
Hazen Wright, Albert Papers, 1820-1960
- Series IX: Lizard Research
  - Notes- Cnemidophorus perplexus (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Notes- Cnemidophorus sexlineatus (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Notes- Cnemidophorus gularis (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Notes- Cnemidophorus grahamii (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Notes-Sauromalus obesus and Dipso-saurus dorsalis (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Notes-Sceloporus elongates and Sceloporus consobrinus consobrinus (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Notes-Scelaporus disparillis and Sceloporus clarkii (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Notes-Sceloporus graciosus (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Notes-Seclaporus (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Notes-Secloporus (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Notes-Secloporus (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Notes-Secloporus (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Notes-Cnemidophorus (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Notes-Crotaphytus (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Notes-Crotaphytus (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Notes-Coleonyx (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Notes-Callisaurus (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Notes-Eumeces (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Notes-Eumeces (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Notes-Gerrhonotus (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Notes-Leiolopisma (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Notes-Alligator mississipiensis and Anniella pulchra (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Notes-Neoseps and Ophisaurus (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Notes-Xantusia and Rhineura (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Notes-Heloderma suspectum (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Notes-Crocodylus and Uta (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Notes-Uta (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Notes-Uta and Uma (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Notes-Holbrookia (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Notes-Holbrookia (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Notes-Phrynosoma (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Notes-Phrynosoma (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Series X: Okefenokee Swamp
  - A Biological Reconnaissance of the Okefinokee Swamp (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Manuscripts (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Manuscripts (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Notes and Maps (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Needham's Notes (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Maps (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Ship Canal Report, 1878-80 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - "Winter Birds of the Okefinokee and Coleraine: A Preliminary Check-List of the Winter Birds of the Interior of Southeastern Georgia" by Frederick V.J. Hebard from the Georgia Society of Naturalists Bulletin No. 3, 1941 (Box 28)
  - "A Biological Reconnaissance of Okefinokee Swamp: The Birds" by A.H. Wright and Francis Harper from The Auk: The Quarterly Journal of Ornithology, Oct., 1913 (Box 28)
  - Field Notebook (Box 28)
  - Record Book (Box 28)
  - Historical Research (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - "The Effects of the Okefenokee Swamp in 1954 and 1955" (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - "A Biological Reconnaissance of the... Reptiles" (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Billy Bowlegs-Part III (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Billy Bowlegs (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Billy Bowlegs (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - A Paper by Alexander B. Klots (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Notes on plants (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Plants (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Notes on Plants (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Articles and magazine accounts of Okefenokee Swamp (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Articles and magazine accounts of Okefenokee Swamp (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - A Listing of Animals (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Notes on Species (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Amphibian Notes (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Amphibian Notes (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Field Notebook, May 25-July 14, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Journal, May 25-July 20, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Journal, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Field Notebook, May 2-July 21, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Field Notebook, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Field Notebook (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Frances Harper's notes, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Field Notebook, Feb.-Aug., 1925 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Catalogue of Okefinokee Reptiles Part II (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Notebook (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous notes and pictures of Okefenokee Swamp (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous notes and pictures of Okefenokee Swamp (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous notes on the Okefenokee Swamp (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Handwritten note on the Okefenokee amphibians, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence
    - Francis Harper, 1912-25 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Personal, 1912 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Business and Personal, 1914-63 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Heckscher Research Foundation (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Business and Personal, 1915-21 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 10 Vols. on Okefinokee Frogs and Reptiles (Box 56)
  - 5 Vols. Okefinokee Frogs (Box 57)
- Series XI: Cornell University Material
  - American Association of University Professors, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Biological Society of Cornell, 1901-02 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Biological Society, 1904-09 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Bailey Hortorium, 1935-41 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Botany Department (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Conservation Committee (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Conservation Committee (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Cosmopolitan Club (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Arboretum, 1937-38 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Club, 1908 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Jugatae Newsletter, 1944-47 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Newsletter of the Department of Geology, 1951-52 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Research Club (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Teacher Training, 1937-38 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Zoology Inventories, 1940-46 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Rolled map of Cornell University in1871 (Box 42)
  - Rolled floor plans of buildings on Cornell University's campus (Box 42)
  - East view of Ithaca and Tompkins County taken in Sept. 1836 (Box 42)
  - Oral Histories
    - Oral History Transcripts-A.H.Wright, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Oral History Transcript-A.H. Wright, Dec. 18, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Oral History Transcript-A.A. and A. H. Wright, Jan. 2, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel I, Dec. 4, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel II, Dec.4 and 11, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel III, Dec. 11, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel III, Dec. 18, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel IV, Dec. 18, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel V, Dec. 18, 1962 (Box 31)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel VI, Jan. 18, 1963 (Box 31)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel VII, Jan. 18, 1963 (Box 31)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel VIII, Jan. 25, 1963-Feb. 4, 1963 (Box 31)
    - Tape Recording of Oral History of A.H. and A.A. Wright-Reel IX, Feb. 4, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Department of Neurology and Vertebrate Zoology
    - Loan Correspondence, 1887-1909 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Funding Correspondence, 1897-1910 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Report, Oct. 26, 1892 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1903-04 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1905-06 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1907-08 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Account Correspondence, 1909-10 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1908-09 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1908-09 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Exchange List, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Inventory of books, charts and photographs, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Inventory of specimens, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Inventory of furniture, rooms and hearths, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Inventory for alcohol, live animals and catalog cards, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Inventory of specimens, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Inventory of specimens (including brains), 1909 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Inventory of specimen rooms 5,7, 8 and 9, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Inventory summary sheets duplicates, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Consolidated inventory, 1909-10 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1943-49 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Zoology newsletter and correspondence, 1944-45 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Teaching Material
    - Miscellaneous material, 1911-46 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1942-52 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1904-56 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous memorabilia, 1904-54 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Cornell Fund and Alumni Association, 1966-69 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Edith Rosella Smelker's Thesis (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous reports (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Teaching material (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Teaching material (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Teaching material (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Teaching material (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Teaching material (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Teaching material (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - "Report of the Committee to Administer the Library.. .New Construction" (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Graduate Students (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - "Some Requests of a Cornell Teacher of Biology" (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Lectures and Notes-Fish, 1923-29 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Lectures and Notes-Fish (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Lectures and Notes-Fish and Toads (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Lectures and Notes-Laboratory Outlines for Zoology 8 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Lecture and Notes-Field Zoology (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Lecture and Notes-Zoology and Mammals (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Lecture and Notes-Zoology 8-reptiles (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Lecture and Notes--Ichthyology (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Ornithology, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Lectures and Notes-Herpetology-amphibians (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Lectures and Notes-Herpetology-Reptilia (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Lectures and Notes-Herpetology-Laboratory notes, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Lectures and Notes-Reptiles (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Lectures and notes-Amphibia, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Lectures and notes (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous, 1904-47 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1946-64 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Resident Instruction, 1936-47 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-55 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Thank You Letters, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Folder 32, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-67 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-65 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Albert Hazen and Anna Allen Wright's School Days
    - Entomology Journal, 1903-05 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Course Book (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Exam, May 29, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - "Compositions" Note Book of Mrs. L.W. Hitchcock Loaned to A. H. Wright (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Anna Allen's Zoology notebook (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Anna Allen's American Literature notebook (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Anna Allen's Report on Insect morphology, 1907 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Anna Allen's Notes on Entomology (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Anna Allen's Notes on Olericulture (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Anna Allen's Notes on Plant Breeding (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Anna Allen's notes on Handicraft (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Anna Allen's Soil Lecture Notes, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Anna Allen's Notes on Nursery and Orchid Practice, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Anna Allen's Outline of Economic Entomology (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Anna Allen's Notes on Psychology, Fall, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Notes on Invertebrate Zoology, Fall, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Anna Allen's notebook on the Literature of Horticulture (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Anna Allen's Essay on Soil, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Anna Allen's Soil Laboratory Notes, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Iris Planting Seedlings, May 19, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - "A List of Books" (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - A.H. Wright's Ornithology Notebook (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - A.H. Wright's Lecture Book, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - A.H. Wright's Ornithology Notebook-Book I (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - A.H. Wright's Ornithology Notebook-Book II (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - A.H. Wright's Ornithology Notebook-Book III (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - A.H. Wright's Course Book (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - A.H. Wright's Notebook (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - A.H. Wright's Geology Notebook, 1901 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Anna Allen's Nature Study Notebook (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Lecture Outlines: Physics Course 1, 1905-06 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - A.H. Wright's debate notes (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Gamma Alpha correspondence, 1907-51 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Gamma Alpha correspondence, 1918-56 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Gamma Alpha correspondence, 1926-56 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Gamma Alpha correspondence, 1951-53 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Gamma Alpha correspondence (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Gamma Alpha correspondence and research (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Gamma Alpha, 1951-57 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Gamma Alpha research (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Gamma Alpha research (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1939-42 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1943-44 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Sigma Xi, 1904-45 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Gamma Alpha Association Certificate of Membership, Apr. 11, 1908 (Box 35)
  - National Research Council
    - Reports, 1935-36 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1935-36 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1935-37 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Agenda, Apr. 24, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and other material, 1931-35 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Reports and correspondence, 1935-39 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Agendas and reports, 1935-36 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Reports, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - "Committee on Biological Abstracts: Report to the Science Advisory Board", Dec. 3, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Organization and members, 1940-41 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Summary statements and reports, 1933-37 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1928-35 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Reports and Summaries, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Agendas and Reports, 1928-35 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Histories of Cornell University
    - Notebook (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Ezra Cornell Research (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Pre-Cornell and Early Cornell Research (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper stories, 1950's (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Pre-Cornell and Early Cornell (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Pre-Cornell and Early Cornell II (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Pre-Cornell and Early Cornell III (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Louis Agassiz Research (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Louis Agassiz Research (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Louis Agassiz Research (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - History of Cornell from 1868 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - History of Cornell from 1869 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - History of Cornell from 1871 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Research material (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Research material (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Research material (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Natural History society notes (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Anti-Cornell 1864-1875 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Genesee College (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Bert G. Wilder Research material (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Manuscripts (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Notes on C.U. career 1901-02 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Cornell Family History (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Louis Agassiz and Ezra Cornell (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous research material (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous research material (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Natural History Society (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Natural History Society (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Natural History Society (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Natural History Society (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Ithaca's Natural History Society (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Ithaca's Natural History Society (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Research Notes (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Research Notes (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Many vols. on Pre-Cornell Studies in History (Box 62)
    - 2 Vols. Pre-Cornell and Early Cornell Studies in History (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Map of Cornell University, November 1, 1871 (Box 42)
    - Map of Camden Town, n.d. (Box 42)
    - Print drawing of Ithaca, September 1836 (Box 42)
    - Blueprint: Main floor Hall of Zoology and Entomology (Box 42)
    - Blueprint: 2nd floor Hall of Zoology and Entomology (Box 42)
    - Blueprint: Basement of Hall of Zoology and Entomology (Box 42)
    - Blueprint: Front elevation of Hall of Zoology and Entomology (Box 42)
    - Blueprint: Lecture/aquarium Room, n.d. (Box 42)
    - Cornell Christmas letters (Box 63)
- Series XII: Published Material
  - "Ithaca Lodge and Cornell University" (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - "The Beautiful Finger Lakes" (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - "Outline of an Introductory Course in Invertebrate Zoology" By John Henry Comstock (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Our Georgia-Florida Frontier: The Okefinokee Swamp Its History and Cartography Vol. 1, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Our Georgia-Florida Frontier: The Okefinokee Swamp Its History and Cartography Vol. 2, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Our Georgia-Florida Frontier: The Okefinokee Swamp Its History and Cartography Vol. 3, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Handbook of American Natural History: Vol. I Handbook of Frogs and Toads, 1933 (Box 5)
  - Handbook of American Natural History: Vol. I Handbook of Frogs and Toads (Box 5)
  - Taber Genealogy: Descendants of Joseph and Philip Sons of Philip Taber, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "New York Historical Source Studies: Part I. Supervisors' Proceedings of Various Counties of New York", 1943 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Our Georgia-Florida Frontier: The Okefenokee Swamp Its History and Cartography Vol. I, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Pigeon by A.H. Wright, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - "New York Historical Source Studies: The Sullivan Expedition of 1779 Regimental Rosters of Men", 1965 (Box 16)
  - "Pre-Cornell and Early Cornell V: Natural History Society of Cornell University.. .", 1954 (Box 16)
  - "Pre-Cornell and early Cornell VI: Cornell's Three Precursors: II. New York State Agricultural College", 1958 (Box 16)
  - "Pre-Cornell and Early Cornell XI: Gamma Alpha Graduate Scientific Fraternity Its Beginning", 1965 (Box 16)
  - "The Sullivan Expedition of 1779"-annotated, 1943 (Box 16)
  - "The Sullivan Expedition of 1779", 1943 (Box 16)
  - From Sea to Shining Sea: A Report on the American Environment-Our Natural Heritage, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Our Wild Orchids: Trails and Portraits, 1929 (Box 16)
  - Old North Hampton in Western New York by Albert Hazen Wright (Box 16)
  - Journal of the Military Expedition Against the Six Nations of Indians in 1779 with Records of Centennial Celebrations (Box 16)
  - "Subject Register of Papers Published in the Transactions and Proceedings of he American Philosophical Society", 1889 (Box 16)
  - Travel Guides & Brochures (Box 46, Folder 9-15)
  - The Sullivan Expedition of 1779, by Albert Hazen Wright, 1943 (Box 46)
  - Journal of the Ohio Herpetological Society, vol. 5, no. 4, December 30, 1966 (Box 46)
  - The Cornell Era, vol. 39, no. 8, May 1907 (Box 46)
  - Subject Register of Papers Published in the Transactions and Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1889 (Box 46)
  - The Method of Making Models from Sheets of Blotting Paper by Susanna Phelps Gage, November 10, 1907 (Box 46)
- Series XIII: Photographs, Photo Albums, and Scrapbooks
  - Family and Friends (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Albert Hazen Wright (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Photographs (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Photographs (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Albert Hazen Wright (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Wright Family (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University Jugatae Banquet, 1915 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Alpha Omicron Phi (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Hazen Family (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Albert Hazen Wright (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Family Photographs (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Cornell University (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Frog Photographs (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Wright-Father of A.H. Wright (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Family Pictures (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Wright Family (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Wright Family Cemetary (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Albert Wright's photographs (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Albert H. Wright (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Field Trips (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Field Trips around the Ithaca area, 1918-38 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Educationl Trips (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Bucknell Trip, 1919-30 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Nature photographs (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Cornell University and surrounding areas (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Professor S.H. Gage (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Photograph of Dennis Wright-Grandfather of Albert H. Wright (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous group photographs (Box 34)
  - Photographs of A.H. and A.A. Wright (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Cornell History Photographs (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Photographs taken in Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of specimen, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Floyd's Island Prairie, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Billy's Island, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Billy's Island, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Flowers, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Floyd's Island Prairie, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Specimen found on Billy's Island, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-People, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Minne's Lake, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Birds, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, 1917-20 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Center Point, Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - A.H. Wright's graduation day (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Capt. F.A. DeVert's Home; Roma, Texas, June 4, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - L. Agassiz (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - L. Agassiz (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - L. Agassiz (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - L. Agassiz (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - L. Agassiz (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - C. Frederick Hartt-from the Cornell Regional History Files (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - C. Frederick Hartt-from the Cornell Regional History Files (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - C. Frederick Hartt-from the Cornell Regional History Files (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - C. Frederick Hartt-from the Cornell Regional History Files (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - C. Frederick Hartt-from the Cornell Regional History Files (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - C. Frederick Hartt-from the Cornell Regional History Files (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Fish, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Fish, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Fish, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Chesser's Island; Frances Harper Photographs, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Billy's Island; Frances Harper Photographs, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Okefenokee Swamp; Frances Harper Photographs, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Specimen found on Billy's Island, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Chesser's Island; Frances Harper Photographs, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Honey Island, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Chesser's Island; Frances Harper Photographs, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Billy's Island; Frances Harper and A.H. Wright Photographs, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Billy's Island; Frances Harper Photographs, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Blackjack Island; Frances Harper Photographs, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 47)